Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- General Cigar Co., 1935-1961, 4 boxes
  - Surveys
    - Miscellaneous, 1936-1950 and undated (Box GC4)
    - Small cigars, 1950 (Box GC4)
    - White Owl dealers, 1950 (Box GC4)
  - Untitled notebooks
    - Advertising expenditures survey, circa 1950 (Box GC4)
    - Important letters, 1931-1949, 3 folders (Box GC4)
      [Includes mention of the reasoning behind targeting women in a major advertising campaign. In that case, cigars were promoted as a gift idea for men, and studies were cited to suggest that White Owl Cigars were less likely to cause bad breath than other brands.]
    - Sales policy, important letters, 1950-1951 (Box GC4)
  - White Owl presentation
    - Charts and advertisements, 1950 (Box GC4)
    - Competitive advertisements and estimates, 1950 (Box GC4)
  - General Cigar Company (Box GC5)
    - Company manual, 1951 (Box GC5)
      [Includes original and facsimile.]
    - White Owl cigar boxes, undated (Box GC6)
- Handy Andy, 1990 and undated, 6 boxes
  [Contains presentation materials, storyboards, promotional posters and sketches for the client Handy Andy. Arranged first by size, and then alphabetically by folder title.]
  - Brochures, 1990 (Box HA1)
  - Campaign notes, undated (Box HA1)
  - Presentation packet, 1990, 2 folders (Box HA1)
  - Print campaign, undated (Box HA1)
  - Display cut-out, undated (Box HA2)
  - Forest City promotions, 1990 (Box HA2)
  - Miscellaneous posters, undated (Box HA2)
  - Posters, undated, 2 folders (Box HA3)
  - Black & Decker poster sketch, undated (Box HA4)
  - Dutch Boy Week poster, undated (Box HA4)
  - Have You Seen What's New Today? (Box HA5)
    - Presentation, undated (Box HA5)
    - Storyboard, 1990 (Box HA5)
  - MinWax poster sketch, undated (Box HA5)
  - Presentation, Schaumburg, IL, 1990, 1-2 of 5 folders (Box HA5)
  - Presentation, Schaumburg, IL, 1990, 3-5 of 5 folders (Box HA6)
  - Rubbermaid poster sketch, undated (Box HA6)
- Hyatt Hotels, 1978-1987, 2 boxes
  - Business travelers responses to Hyatt Food and Beverage Operations Phase II, 1985 (Box HY1)
  - Clippings, 1977-1983 (Box HY1)
  - Communications check, 1986 (Box HY1)
  - Exploratory research to evaluate travelers' potential acceptance of new Hyatt Hotel concepts, 1984 (Box HY1)
  - Hotel industry background overview, 1978 (Box HY1)
  - Hyatt Hotels 1984 tracking study, Wave III, 1985 (Box HY1)
  - Hyatt Regency Grand Cypress study, Wave I, 1986 (Box HY1)
  - Look at travel agent usage of the Hotel and Travel Index and advertising in the Index, 1986 (Box HY1)
  - Midweek studies, 1986-87, 2 folders (Box HY1)
  - New hotel concept feasibility study, 1985 (Box HY1)
  - Palm Beaches customer survey results, 1984 (Box HY2)
  - Palm Beaches Midweek and Gold Passport customers results, 1984 (Box HY2)
  - Review of selected new hotel products and their attributes relative to the Hyatt One and Hyatt Two concepts, 1985 (Box HY2)
  - Topline findings: Hyatt retirement living complexes, 1986 (Box HY2)
  - Tracking study, wave V, 1986 (Box HY2)
  - Trade directory evaluation among travel agents and corporate meeting planners, 1984 (Box HY2)
  - Weekend promotion study, 1986 (Box HY2)
- International Banana Association, 2001-2003 [RESTRICTED]
  - General Files, 2001-2003
    - Banana analysis: teen segment, 2002, 2 folders (Box IBA1)
    - Banana attitude and usage research, 2002 (Box IBA1)
    - Banana cross tabs, 2001, 5 folders (Box IBA1)
    - Banana research, 2002, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box IBA1)
    - Banana research (continued), 2002, 3 of 3 folders (Box IBA2)
    - Consumption campaign, 2001 (Box IBA2)
    - Creative review, 2001 (Box IBA2)
    - Focus group questionnaire: Chicago, 2002, 2 folders (Box IBA2)
    - Qualitative and quantitative research2002-2003, 3 folders (Box IBA2)
  - Audiovisual Materials
    - Originals (Closed to Research)
      - Audiocassettes
        - OR1. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR2. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 4 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR3. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR4. Focus Group, Bananas, Robert C, 1/30/01. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR5. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/30/01, 12 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR6. Focus Group, Snacks, Kathleen S, 1/31/01, 2-8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR7. Focus Group, Snacks, Janet O, 1/31/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR8. Focus Group, Snacks, Matthew A, 1/31/01, 4 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR9. Focus Group, Snacks, Eric Y, 1/31/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR10. Focus Group, Snacks, Ann M, 2/1/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR11. Focus Group, Snacks, Devin S, 2/1/01, 4 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR12. Focus Group, Snacks, Shawn S, 2/1/01, 6 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR13. Focus Group, Snacks, Alexis M, 2/1/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR14. Focus Group, Bananas, 3/8/02, 12 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR15. Focus Group, Bananas, 3/8/02, 2 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR16. Focus Group, Bananas, 3/8/02, 6 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
        - OR17. Focus Group, Bananas, 3/8/02, 8 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: C120. (Box IBA3)
      - DVD
        - OR18. Focus Group, Banana, Tuesday, 3/6/02. Created: 2002. TRT: Unknown. (Box IBA4)
        - OR19. Focus Group, Banana, Tuesday, 3/6/02 (Dup of OR1). Created: 2002. TRT: Unknown. (Box IBA4)
      - U-Matic Videocassettes
        - OR20. Chicago, 3/8/02, 12 p.m., 1 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR21. Chicago, 3/8/02, 12 p.m., 2 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR22. Chicago, 3/8/02, 2 p.m., 1 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR23. Chicago, 3/8/02, 2 p.m., 2 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR24. Chicago, 3/8/02, 6 p.m., 1 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR25. Chicago, 3/8/02, 6 p.m., 2 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR26. Chicago, 3/8/02, 8 p.m., 1 of 2, Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR27. Chicago, 3/8/02, 8 p.m., 2 of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR28. Copy of 1. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
        - OR29. Copy of 2. Created: 2002. TRT: 60:00. (Box IBA4)
      - VHS Videocassettes
        - OR30. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR31. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR32. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 6 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR33. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/29/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR34. Focus Group, Bananas, Robert C, 1/30/01. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR35. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/30/01, 12 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR36. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/30/01, 2-10 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR37. Focus Group, Bananas, 1/30/01, 6 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR38. Focus Group, Snacks, Janet O, 1/31/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR39. Focus Group, Snacks, Matthew A, 1/31/01, 4 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR40. Focus Group, Snacks, Kathleen S, 1/31/01, 2-8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR41. Focus Group, Snacks, Eric Y, 1/31/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR42. Focus Group, Snacks, Ann M, 2/1/01, 2 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA5)
        - OR43. Focus Group, Snacks, Devin S, 2/1/01, 4 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
        - OR44. Focus Group, Snacks, Alexis M, 2/1/01, 8 p.m. Created: 2001. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
        - OR45. Fieldwork Chicago--O'Hare, Banana, 3/8/02, 12 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
        - OR46. Fieldwork Chicago--O'Hare, Banana, 3/8/02, 2 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
        - OR47. Fieldwork Chicago--O'Hare, Banana, 3/8/02, 6 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
        - OR48. Fieldwork Chicago--O'Hare, Banana, 3/8/02, 8 p.m. Created: 2002. TRT: T120. (Box IBA6)
- International Business Machines Corporation (IBM), 1959-1993, 7 boxes
  - General Files
    - Advertising and Promotion Guide, undated (Box IBM1)
      [Policy manual of IBM Corporate Advertising Department]
    - Agency status meeting, undated (Box IBM2)
    - Burrelle advertising analysis reports, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - Clippings, 1959-1987, 8 folders (Box IBM2)
    - Competitive advertising tracking system proposal, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - Competitive creative printouts, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - Computer 101, undated (Box IBM2)
    - Confidential disclosure agreement, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - Copy examples (some items removed to Oversize Materials, Box IB7), 1985-1986 and undated (Box IBM2)
    - Corporate communications task document, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - DEC advertising overview, 1986 (Box IBM2)
      [Digital Equipment Corporation was a leading IBM competitor. Report was prepared by Doyle Dane Bernbach agency.]
    - General Profile of Computer Decision Makers, 1987 (Box IBM2)
    - IBM 1986 Annual Meeting, remarks by John Akers, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - IBM 370 processor follow-on products, 1986 (Box IBM2)
    - IBM business conduct guidelines, 1983 (Box IBM2)
    - IBM focus groups, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - IBM publications, 1984-1987 (Box IBM3)
    - IBM technical support, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - IBM...Yesterday and Today, undated (Box IBM3)
    - Industry marketing presentation, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Industry seminars, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Information Systems Group (ISG) 1985 review/1986 requirements, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Information Systems Group (ISG) strategic directions, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - JWT Briefing, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - JWT/IBM management interviews, undated (Box IBM3)
    - JWT presentation to IBM, undated (Box IBM3)
    - JWT Resources at Work, undated (Box IBM3)
    - K-12 media recommendations, 1987 (Box IBM3)
    - Learning plan, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Local advertising, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Marketing image copy presentation, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box IBM3)
    - Measurement plan to assess IBM image, 1986 (Box IBM3)
    - Mid-range competitive positioning, undated (Box IBM4)
    - Mid-range systems agenda, undated (Box IBM4)
    - National Branch Managers Meeting, V.J. Goldberg remarks, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - Partnership to Have, 1986, 2 folders (Box IBM4)
    - Production--Southern Pacific Railroad, 1985-1987 (Box IBM4)
    - Relational Productivity, undated (Box IBM4)
    - Research, IBM image study, 1985 (Box IBM4)
    - Research, Recent Changes in Large Customer Perceptions of Value Added, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - Review Board briefing, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - ROLM product directions, 1986 (Box IBM4)
      [ROLM was a subsidiary of IBM]
    - ROLM publications, 1985 (Box IBM4)
    - Satisfaction survey, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission--Form 10-K, 1984 (Box IBM4)
    - Slides, undated (Box IBM4)
    - Strategy Review Board #2, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - Systrack/Adtrack, 1986 (Box IBM4)
    - Tear sheets, 1984-1987 (Box IBM5)
    - Telecommunications industry competitive analysis, 1986 (Box IBM5)
    - Telecommunications overview, 1986 (Box IBM5)
  - Audiovisual Materials (Originals closed; need use copies)
    - Akers, undated. Format: Umatic. (Box IBM6)
    - Clutter reel, revised master, undated. Format: Umatic. (Box IBM6)
    - Competitive reel, 1987. Format: Umatic. (Box IBM6)
    - Focus group selects, undated. Format: Umatic. (Box IBM6)
    - Focus group selects for strategy, 1986. Format: Umatic. (Box IBM6)
    - IBM Product Line Part 1: The Machine Room, 1984. Format: Umatic. Trt: 35:37 (Box IBM6)
    - IBM Product Line Part 2: The Network, 1985. Format: Umatic. Trt: 34:00 (Box IBM6)
    - IBM Product Line Part 3: The Independents, 1985. Format: Umatic. Trt: 34:00 (Box IBM6)
    - Marketing Image, 1987. Format: VHS. (Box IBM6)
    - On the Couch, 1993. Format: NTSC. Trt: 13:40. JWT London (Box IBM6)
  - Oversize Materials
    - Copy examples, 1985-1986 and undated (Box IBM7)
    - Industry seminars, 1986 (Box IBM7)
- Kellogg Company, 1961-1994, 8 boxes
  - General Files
    - 50th anniversary, 1986 (Box KL1)
    - JWT Account Manager's Guide, 1989 (Box KL1)
    - Magazine advertising estimates, 1981 (Box KL1)
    - Memoranda, 1983-1985 (Box KL1)
    - Micro-marketing analysis, 1990 (Box KL1)
    - Miscellaneous, 1984-1985 (Box KL1)
    - Newspaper and magazine advertisements, 1961-1986 (Box KL1)
    - Research audit, 1990 (Box KL1)
    - Sales meeting materials, 1984-1985 (Box KL1)
  - Cereals
    - General
      - Bridge campaign--international: Estimates, publishing instructions, 1980-1981 (Box KL1)
      - Consumption study, 1984 (Box KL1)
      - Marketing plans and strategizing, 1983-1986, 2 folders (Box KL2)
      - Performance data, 1984-1986 (Box KL2)
    - Apple Raisin Crisp
      - Assessments and reviews, 1984-1986 (Box KL2)
      - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box KL2)
      - Competition, 1984-1985 (Box KL2)
      - Copy strategy, 1984-1986 (Box KL2)
      - Creative, 1985 (Box KL2)
      - Flanker product--Banana Date Crisp, 1984 (Box KL2)
      - Marketing pre-planning, 1985-1986 (Box KL2)
      - Marketing plans, 1984-1986, 1 of 4 folders (Box KL2)
      - Marketing plans, 1984-1986 (continued), 2-4 of 4 folders (Box KL3)
      - Marketing research: Communications tests, 1984-1985, 3 folders (Box KL3)
      - Marketing research: Product tests, 1983-1985, 1-2 of 3 folders (Box KL3)
      - Marketing research: Product tests, 1983-1985 (continued), 3 of 3 folders (Box KL4)
      - Media plan 1985, 1985 (Box KL4)
      - Miscellaneous, 1985 (Box KL4)
      - Packaging, 1984-1985 (Box KL4)
      - Television advertisements, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box KL4)
    - Bran Flakes
      - General, 1984-1985 (Box KL4)
    - Corn Flakes
      - General, 1985-1986 (Box KL4)
    - Crispix
      - General, 1983-1985 (Box KL4)
    - Fruitful Bran
      - Analysis and reviews, 1984-1986 (Box KL4)
      - Budget, 1983-1986 (Box KL4)
      - Competition: Performance data, 1983-1986 (Box KL5)
      - Copy strategy, 1983-1985 (Box KL5)
      - Creative, 1984-1985 (Box KL5)
      - Estimates, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box KL5)
      - Flanker, 1985-1986 (Box KL5)
      - Marketing plans, 1983-1986, 1-3 of 4 folders (Box KL5)
      - Marketing plans, 1983-1986 (continued), 4 of 4 folders (Box KL6)
      - Marketing research, 1983-1986 (Box KL6)
      - Marketing research: Focus groups, 1985 (Box KL6)
      - Marketing strategies, 1983-1986, 2 folders (Box KL6)
      - Media plans, 1984-1986 (Box KL6)
      - Packaging, 1984-1986 (Box KL6)
      - Performance data--productivity figures, 1983-1987 (Box KL6)
      - Positioning concepts, 1986-1987 (Box KL7)
      - Print advertising, 1984-1985 (Box KL7)
      - Project Bard, 1983-1984 (Box KL7)
      - Project improvement and line extension, 1984-1986 (Box KL7)
      - Sales meetings, 1983-1985 (Box KL7)
      - Strategy meetings, 1985-1987 (Box KL7)
      - Studies, tests, and planning, 1983-1986 (Box KL7)
      - Summaries, 1984-1985 (Box KL7)
      - Television media: Authorizations, 1983-1985, 1 of 2 folders (Box KL7)
      - Television media: Authorizations, 1983-1985 (continued), 2 of 2 folders (Box KL8)
      - Television media: Bushels of Taste/Peaches campaign, 1984-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Television media: Commercials and network schedules, 1983-1986 (Box KL8)
    - Nutri-Grain
      - Analysis and reviews, 1984-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Budget, 1984-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Competition, 1984 (Box KL8)
      - Estimates, 1984-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Flanker products, 1984-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Media plans, 1983-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Packaging, 1983-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Performance data, 1984 (Box KL8)
      - Print advertising, 1985 (Box KL8)
      - Strategies, 1983-1985 (Box KL8)
      - Television media, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box KL8)
- Kraft Foods, 1922-2004, bulk 1974-2004, 10 boxes
  - Open Files
    - Account history--Phenix Cheese, 1922-1926 (Box KR1)
    - Advertisements
      - Canadian magazine (Philadelphia Cream Cheese), 1998 (Box KR1)
      - International magazine, 1998-2002 (Box KR1)
      - International postcards, undated (Box KR1)
      - Kraft Singles, 1981 (Box KR1)
    - [Advertising fact sheet, 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Advertising fact sheet on Miracle Whip, 2003: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - Articles, 1950s-1980s, 4 folders (Box KR1)
    - Background report, 1964 (Box KR1)
    - [Body Builder for Kids campaign, 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Business Results, 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Creative presentation to Mike Polk (Kraft Singles), circa 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Creative Review, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.], 3 folders (Box KR1)
    - [Creative Review, 2003: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.], 2 folders (Box KR1)
    - [Creative Review, 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.], 2 folders (Box KR1)
    - [Creative Review--Philadelphia UK, 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Creative Review presented to Irene Rosenfeld, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Fast Adapt case studies, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Getting to Heaven, circa 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR4.] (Box KR1)
    - [Getting to World-Class, 2003: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR1)
    - History of Miracle Whip, 1960, 1966, 2 folders (Box KR1)
    - History of Velveeta, 1957 (Box KR1)
    - Jacobs Coffee, undated (in Russian) (Box KR1)
    - [JWT Welcomes Kraft, 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR1)
    - [Kraft Singles re-launch strategy, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR1)
    - Kraft's Role in the Frozen Food Market, 1961 (Box KR2)
    - Labels, undated (Box KR2)
    - Likeability study, 1990 (Box KR2)
    - Management review, 1983 (Box KR2)
    - Marketing procedures, 1974 (Box KR2)
    - [Media plan with slides, 1998: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR2)
    - [Mexico-Puerto Rico agency briefing, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR2)
    - Memoranda
      - 75th anniversary, 1977 (Box KR2)
      - [For Ron Burns, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR2)
      - Re Burnett, Carol, 1983-1984 (Box KR2)
      - Re Crosby, Bing, 1975-1977 (Box KR2)
      - Re Hope, Bob, 1979 (Box KR2)
    - Miracle Whip case study, 1957 (Box KR2)
    - [Miracle Whip marketing orientation, 2006: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5 (Box KR3)
    - [Pan-Asian campaign, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
    - Philadelphia Cream Cheese
      - [Canada/U.S. share, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
      - [Concept plans, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
      - [Heaven launch in Australia, circa 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
      - [Media objectives, 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
      - [Meeting Future Challenges, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
      - [Memoranda, 2002-2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
    - Presentations
      - Branding ideas (South Africa), undated (Box KR3)
      - Creativity and Innovation in Media Planning, 1992 (Box KR3)
      - Media Seminar, 1992 (Box KR3)
    - Publications
      - Annual Meetings, 1976-1980 (Box KR3)
      - Annual report, 1987 (Box KR3)
      - Children's books, 2002 (Box KR3)
      - Kraftsman, 1974-1975 (Box KR3)
      - Kraft Works, 2001-2003 (Box KR3)
      - Nutrition, cookbooks, 1972-1986 (Box KR3)
      - Recipe books--International, 1995-2002 (Box KR3)
    - Research reports, 1986 (Box KR3)
    - [Ritz Crackers Canada/U.S. share, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
    - Television
      - Bing Crosby Special, 1977, 2 folders (Box KR3)
      - Network television, 1973-1976, 7 folders (Box KR3)
      - Spanish television script, undated (Box KR3)
    - [Thompson Total Branding, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.] (Box KR3)
    - [Worldwide advertising review, 2004: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR5.], 3 folders (Box KR3)
    - Worldwide Overview
      - [For Abelendo, Gustavo, 2003: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR6.] (Box KR3)
      - [For JWT Toronto, 2002: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR6.] (Box KR3)
      - [For McQuin, Debra, 2000: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR6.] (Box KR3)
      - [For Schweitzer, Peter, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR6.] (Box KR3)
      - [For Webb, William, 2001: Removed to Restricted Materials, Box KR6.] (Box KR3)
  - Restricted Files
    - Advertising fact sheet, 2004 (Box KR4)
    - Advertising fact sheet on Miracle Whip, 2003 (Box KR4)
    - Body Builder for Kids campaign, 2000 (Box KR4)
    - Business results, 2000 (Box KR4)
    - Creative presentation to Mike Polk (Kraft Singles), circa 2000 (Box KR4)
    - Creative review, 2002, 3 folders (Box KR4)
    - Creative review, 2003, 2 folders (Box KR4)
    - Creative review, 2004, 2 folders (Box KR4)
    - Creative review--Philadelphia UK, 2000 (Box KR4)
    - Creative review presented to Irene Rosenfeld, 2002 (Box KR4)
    - Fast Adapt case studies, 2001 (Box KR4)
    - Getting to Heaven, circa 2004 (Box KR4)
    - Getting to World-Class, 2003 (Box KR5)
    - JWT Welcomes Kraft, 2004 (Box KR5)
    - Kraft Singles re-launch strategy, 2001 (Box KR5)
    - Media plan with slides, 1998 (Box KR5)
    - Memoranda For Ron Burns, 2002 (Box KR5)
    - Mexico-Puerto Rico agency briefing, 2001 (Box KR5)
    - Miracle Whip marketing orientation, 2006 (Box KR5)
    - Pan-Asian campaign, 2001 (Box KR5)
    - Philadelphia Cream Cheese
      - Canada/U.S. share, 2002 (Box KR5)
      - Concept plans, 2001 (Box KR5)
      - Heaven launch in Australia, circa 2004 (Box KR5)
      - Media objectives, 2000 (Box KR5)
      - Meeting Future Challenges, 2002 (Box KR5)
      - Memoranda, 2002-2004 (Box KR5)
    - Ritz Crackers Canada/U.S. share, 2002 (Box KR5)
    - Thompson Total Branding, 1997 (Box KR5)
    - Worldwide advertising review, 2004, 3 folders (Box KR5)
    - Worldwide overview (Box KR6)
      - For Abelendo, Gustavo, 2003 (Box KR6)
      - For JWT Toronto, 2002 (Box KR6)
      - For McQuin, Debra, 2000 (Box KR6)
      - For Schweitzer, Peter, 2001 (Box KR6)
      - For Webb, William, 2001 (Box KR6)
  - Restricted Audiovisual Materials
    [Audiovisual materials relating to corporate business are closed for 15 years from the date of creation. In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to research until use copies can be made. Contact Research Services for more information.]
    - Creative Review. 2001 Format: CD-R. (Box KR7)
    - Creative Review. 2002 Format: CD-R. (Box KR7)
    - Creative Review. 2003 Format: VHS. (Box KR7)
    - Creative Review presented to Irene Rosenfeld. 2002 Format: U-matic. (Box KR7)
    - International Advertising Update presented to Gustavo Abelendo. 2003 Format: U-matic. (Box KR7)
    - International Review 2003. Undated. Format: DVD. (Box KR7)
    - Mid-Year Summit--Chicago. 2004 Format: Betacam PAL. (Box KR7)